So today's a big day. It finally finally
happened. GPT5, you can see it right
there, is finally out. It's available in
chat GPT. It's available through the
API. And I've been waiting to make this
video to tell you all about it and to
discuss what this means for most users
since well, early 2024 really. That's
the first time they kind of teased it.
What we're going to talk about today is
first of all that this is the brand new
model that is going to be the default in
chat GPT. Matter of fact, they nuked all
other models. This is the only one you
get to choose from here on out. No more
thinking selection. And also, it's
available across all plans. So, if
you're a free user, this is probably the
happiest day for you when it comes to AI
releases ever because they're making
this available to everybody, ranging
from the free all the way to the $200
pro plan. What my plan is for this video
is I'm not going to run elaborate
benchmarks. not going to be building
esoteric games and physics simulations
and seeing if it's incrementally better
than what we saw before. I'll have
multiple examples in the end where we'll
be comparing it to the competition. I
think that matters. But mostly I want to
answer this one question that I have
written down on my paper here. And that
is what does this mean for most people?
What does this mean for your mom? What
does this mean for people at work? What
does this mean for students? What does
this mean for most people that don't
spend their entire free time nerding out
over AI and figuring out which model is
the best one in this particular week?
And I think there's a lot here, okay?
Not just that this is available to
everybody, but it also brings new
capabilities and merges a lot of old
capabilities into one system now. And my
hope is that this piece of content is
going to help you navigate that. And
it's and also I hope that this is going
to be a piece of content that will help
people who might have been sleeping on
the releases of the past few weeks or
months catch up and really get up to
speed so you don't feel behind and you
realize where we're at in AI space and
how to use this to your very own
advantage. So with that being said,
let's dive right into it. I'll start out
with summarizing what this release is
all about. There's a 90-minute live
stream if you want all the details. I'll
give you a quick summary here of what
matters. Then we'll be moving on to some
of the facts around it, like what's new
and how that realistically compares to
some of the competition and some of the
competition's best releases. Matter of
fact, this week, if you're not not
familiar, we had two big releases with
Opus 4.1 anthropics best model coming
out and Gemini deep think deep think
finally coming out. They announced this
um a few months back. It's out and then
OpenAI came out with this model which is
better at most things. That's kind of
the summary from what we've seen so far.
But in the end of this video, we'll be
going in and we'll be practically
looking at a few examples that matter to
me. We won't be looking at some of these
esoteric benchmarks or like test cases
that nobody would really be doing. I
want to look at a few things and that's
what we're going to be doing. I want to
look at the writing style. I want to
look at its ability to generate ideas
and I want to look at its ability to
recreate one of the demos, the one with
the castle we saw in the live stream. I
thought that one was really impressive.
I want to see how well Claude does at
that. We're going to compare that. So,
without further ado, let's dive right
into kind of the summary and the
overview of what GPT5 is about and what
you can expect. Before we do that, I
want to say one last thing and that is
where I'm coming from as you know your
presenter here today. And I want to
point out that I'm coming at it from a
power user perspective. At this point in
time, I did the rough calculation. I
have around 2,000 somewhere between two
and 3,000 hours just inside of chat GPT.
and its competitors like Claude or
Gemini. That's not even including the
development, the API side and usage of
these models. I've been doing this every
day since the release day of chat GPT. I
really I'm an obsessive type and I kind
of went all in on this. So, I'm going to
be giving you my perspective but with a
lot of empathy for somebody's
perspective who might just be coming in
or might just be catching up with this
topic. Okay. My primary use cases, I
think this is important, are not
development use cases. They're not
medical use cases. They're not I'm not
doing physics with this stuff. I'm
writing, I'm planning, I'm ideulating,
I'm using it for entrepreneurship, I'm
using it for marketing, I'm using it for
psychological tasks. I love that. Those
are my personal interests and that's
where I find it really empowers me. So
that's kind of the angle that I'm taking
here. a power user who is a more common
perspective on this rather than one of a
developer or one of a physicist or
mathematician evaluating these models.
So first of all, this is the flagship
model from OpenAI and it's going to be
replacing all other models in Chat GPT.
Again, no more other models. That mess
that we had there with the model
selector and thinking models,
non-thinking models and coding
specialized models, and this one is good
at psychology, and this one uses web
search. Well, no, that's all gone. GBD5,
that's all you get. And it automatically
selects between the various tools it
has. It's still it has all the tools
now. So you get uh web browsing, you get
custom instructions, you get the canvas,
you get the code interpreter. All of
that is built into one thing. If all of
those don't mean much to you, don't
worry about it. You're kind of just by
using this product, you'll kind of learn
about them. For example, the canvas is
like a word editor inside of chat GPT
and custom instructions is sort of like
giving it an extra prompt in addition to
what you're already sending it. But I
think the massive massive thing here is
and we'll get to kind of the benefits of
this whole thing for the users here but
I really want to point out I think for
people who are not extremely versed in
how to use these models this is going to
be so much more intuitive right you
don't need super long super precise
prompts to get good results out of
models like O3 previously and this just
builds on that okay this is not release
chat this is not GPT3.5 from 2022 where
it really makes a difference if your
prompt is this long or this long. Um,
and the shorter prompts are just not
going to give you the results. This
works differently. So, I think it's a
huge upgrade for free users. And that's
going to be kind of the story of this
entire video. I'm going to be kind of
pointing that out from multiple
perspectives. Yet, power users are also
happy to see this because one amazing
thing is there's no more thinking.
There's no more selection between, hey,
do I want a thinking model? Do I want a
non-thinking model? Matter of fact, this
is not even too new. If you paid close
attention inside of chat GPT over the
recent months they had this change where
even GBD40 was thinking at times it
never spent minutes thinking but it
often spent like 10 15 20 seconds
thinking. So they already implemented
this ability to automatically decide if
it should just give you an answer right
away or if it should think for 15
seconds before it gives you an answer.
Now this is fully integrated and you
don't even get a choice. It just decides
on its own if it should be thinking or
if it will just give you a quick answer.
If you ask it's a fact of like how many
people live in New York like it
shouldn't be thinking for a minute or
two. Um some of the previous models like
03 Pro that question right there would
have thought for like five minutes and
then it gave you the number that GP40
could have given you right away. So now
it's all merged into one thing. You just
get the answer with hopefully the right
thinking depth. Now let's talk
benchmarks. I pulled up the releases
from this week that matter which is uh
Entropics. These are the main two
competitors. Thropic and Google Gemini,
their benchmarks in some areas are still
better. Uh GPD5 like long story short,
GPD5 wins on most of them, but on
specific benchmarks, these other models
are still better. For for example, on AM
2025 mathematics, well, deep think
reaches 99.2. If we look at uh
competition math right here, you'll see
GBT5 with no tools is at 94. Excellent
result. But yeah, Gemini wins on that
one. Agentic tool use um anthropic wins
on one of these and loses on the other
one of them. Okay. And then there's a
few that um open didn't even include
like terminal bench which is the
terminal usage there. Um I suppose
Claude would just win otherwise they
would include it. And then there was one
more actually I pointed it out MML
which is multilingual QA. So like if you
want to do multiple languages, these
other models might be performing better
than GP5. I mean there has to be some
trade-offs, right? So they didn't even
include those. On some of the other
things, a lot of the coding benchmarks,
it just straight out wins. Okay, but
again, we're not here to talk about
benchmarks. I just wanted to highlight
that they're best on most of them now,
but not all of them. And some of these
competing models when it just comes to
benchmarks still win on some on certain
measurements. So what really matters is
how it performs in the real world. What
really matters is, hey, are you going to
be gravitating towards this product? Is
it going to be making your life better?
Is it going to be making you more
productive, freeing up more time to do
things that you actually care about
rather than maybe some data analysis or
some research and tedious tasks at the
computer? And that's what we'll try to
answer in the last segment of this video
where we look at multiple examples. But
now I want to actually talk about some
of the features and some of the things
they pointed out during the live stream.
Okay, so I have like three bullet points
right here that I want to kind of touch
on and discuss and then we'll get into
the demo part. So one of the things that
this will be doing is that it's supposed
to have way less hallucinations. I think
that's actually really exciting and
that's the type of announcement we
haven't seen out of any competing
company yet. I haven't seen Google come
out or anthropic come out or any of the
Chinese models come out with like an
announcement that hey this model
hallucinates way less. It's more
reliable. Open AI is kind of a first on
that. And when I talk to people, it's
one of the it's one of the top things
that I hear from people as a concern
about AI. Like it hallucinates a lot.
How can I trust it? I can't trust it,
right? It's just going to confidently
give me wrong facts. I still need to
like get the right facts. I can't just
like it. I don't want it to lie to me
confidently. So, it's doing better on
that. They quantified this in some
numbers. But I think this is one of the
things that only time will show. I don't
dare to kind of like judge this today
from the first results from the release.
But that's really an exciting direction
that OpenAI is taking. I hope we see
more of that. Secondly, they're saying
it's more emotionally resonant than
before, meaning it has very high EQ and
meaning it will pick up on the user's
behavior. Matter of fact, there was a
release um an announcement from this
week where they're actually including a
little box that pops up if you're
talking to chat for too long that says
like, "Hey, are you sure? Like you want
to keep chatting? It's been a while.
Maybe take a little break." And this in
combination with this announcement or
that GPD5 is supposed to be even more
emotionally resonant than before. I'm
really excited for it. One little side
note is they had this um model called
4.5. Most people didn't use it. I I
actually used it a ton. I really liked
it for all my psychological use cases
where I kind of like simulated different
scenarios or I had different smart
people discuss an idea that I was
interested in or I used it as a coach on
several like entrepreneurial decisions
on all those. The 4.5 model was the best
until Claude for Opus came out. Then I
switched to that because I really just
like the human aspect of it. The way it
sounds, the way it gives concise advice
and doesn't like overexlain. I really
like that. But 4.5 was amazing and this
is supposed to mirror those
capabilities. When they used this
language, when OpenAI used this language
for the first time, it was the 4.5
release and now they said it again,
emotionally resonant. So you can expect
that it's going to be a better friend.
It's going to be a better u human. It's
going to be a better AI. It's going to
be a better companion for humans. I
think that's the right wording right
there, isn't it? Okay. So we can expect
that and we can look at some of that in
the writing example here in a second.
But I have three more bullet points
here. One of them is um also an
interesting one that we've never seen
before. It's supposed to be less
deceptive. Meaning that when it doesn't
know the result, it's not just going to
stand there and pretend like it knows it
every single time. Sure, still going to
happen a lot and it is a big problem.
Sometimes it just doesn't know how to
get to the right answer and it just
gives it to you and it's like, "Hey,
here it is."
And then you're sitting there like,
"Okay, cool. Thank you." You work with
it. One time I pulled up a quote that I
was even using in a lecture and then
after doing some research and like
trying to find the source of the quote I
realized it completely hallucinated that
thing and it confidently presented it to
me as if it was like it made like it
used a real institute of like some
standardization and and whatever but
like the quote was made up so that
happens and now it's supposed to be
better one more thing two more things
that are supposed to be better um it's
way better at medical use cases
apparently this is something I can't
test right Now, I don't have the
expertise, but we'll put it put together
a set of test prompts and then either in
tomorrow's news you can use video or in
next week's news you can use video, our
show that we do every Friday that I do
every Friday. U me and the team research
like all the AI releases and show you
the ones that you can actually use and
then u practical applications for them.
Shout out to news you can use. You can
check that check that out. Subscribe to
the channel to check that out every
single Friday. But medical use cases
we'll be looking at there. I think you
kind of need to get a bit more nuanced
and test a bit more in depth to really
have an opinion on that. And then
lastly, um I want to point out that
actually only the pro plan is going to
have deep thinking. Now, if you're not
aware, deep thinking is like this
capability that you can enable in other
assistants or you could already enable.
I mean, Gemini literally released a
model called deep think now. So, that's
what it does by default. and Claude, you
can kind of go in here and yeah, do
extended thinking. They had this
capability already. Now only the pro
plan is going to have that. So that's a
$200 plan and it's sort of the
equivalent of previously uh 03 pro if
you're familiar with that. Also only
available on the free $100 plan, $200
plan. So that's where it like thinks for
five minutes before it gives you a
result. Probably only relevant if you're
doing maths and physics, maybe
development. I think on development it
can be actually really useful but nobody
really used OpenAI models for
development up until now. They used
Gemini or claude. This might change now
because like they made a big point out
of development being a big thing. And
those are all the kind of features you
can expect. Now two more unexpected
things that they mentioned and I think
most people overheard. So I think these
are good and then we'll get into the
practical part here, right? That most
people are probably waiting for. So
first of all they said there's going to
be GPT swift voice. So if you're not
familiar, GPTs are their chat bots
within chat GPT. You can give custom
instructions. They can do actions.
Matter of fact, in our community, we've
been building interesting things with
GPT since the day of release. And even
now, we're doing things where like you
can daily journal with the GPT and then
it saves it to your own note takingaking
app or database and then you can pull in
like previous notes and like work with
them. You can do really cool things with
GPT. GPTs, that's just one example.
They're getting voice mode. So if you
want if you have a daily journaling
voice node uh GPT that is going to be
saving uh your journal entries to your
very own database your very own notion
for example or whatever you might be
using now you can just turn on voice
mode and like talk to it. You can just
blabber as I am right now. You can kind
of just do that. For me and many others
that is the most natural interface. Um
one thing about talking that I love is
you can talk faster than you can type
even if you're a fast typer. And a lot
of times when I type, I feel like my
thoughts get ahead of my uh ability to
type. So talking is huge. And with GPTs,
we're going to have GPD5, the
connectivity, and we're going to have
the voice mode, which is amazing. I
think this is really going to like
revive GPTs a bit. I hope. I love GPS. I
still use them. They're so useful. And
talking about connectivity, this is my
very last unexpected point that some
people might have missed. Somewhere in
the middle of the presentation, they
just quickly mentioned this. They're
gonna have calendar and Gmail connectors
in GPT5.
So, you're gonna have a true personal
assistant where you connect it to your
calendar and your emails and you're
going to be able to check in in the
morning. Maybe set up a custom GPT and
just ask, "Hey, what's up? What are we
doing today?" And it just gives you the
rundown autonomously right there inside
of Chat GPT. Um, for anybody thinking
right now, for for any power user
thinking, um, I'm going to go over it's
not shipped in my uh in here, we're
going to be using it through the API.
But for anybody thinking, hey, Eigor,
don't we already have those connectors?
Yeah, we do for deep research and the
agent, but not for chat GPT. If I look
at connectors right here, uh, where is
it? Data controls connectors. You can
see Gmail is connected, but it's only
available for deep research and agent
mode. next week. So that is like mid
August. It's going to be shipping to all
plans including um well it's going to be
shipping to the pro and the plus plan,
not to the free plan. So if you're
paying $20 a month, you're going to get
to connect this to your calendar, to
your emails, and use some of its
capabilities.
But now let's finally try it. Let's give
it a shot. Few things I want to try
here. Okay, first of all, I always
really care about the writing style of
these things. I I feel like if the model
sounds bad, I'm going to be using it way
less just because so much of what I do
is related to writing. And even when I
just read the results and they just
sound like crap, I don't like it. That's
why I was or like I am a big Claude fan
because it just sounds human. It sounds
natural. It keeps things concise. I like
that. With GPT, I really liked 4.5. I
liked 03 for its web search. But yeah,
let's just give this a shot and have a
look at a basic writing prompt that I
just ran right in here. Um, I always use
this one. If you follow the channel for
a while, you might notice already. Write
me an email to my boss about the broken
coffee machine in our office. And then I
just ran this in here and I'm going to
put these up side by side. I'm going to
have the Clawed Opus 4.1 result that
released a few days ago. And I'm going
to have the GPT5 result here on the
left. And this is going to be my very
first look at the writing style. So
exciting to see how this actually
performs. Okay, so let's start by just
reading this broken coffee machine in
the office is the subject. And again,
this is just one example. Please make up
your own mind. I am going to give my
opinion because that's why I'm here. No.
Hi, boss's name. I wanted to let you
know that the coffee machine in our
office is currently not working. It
seems to have brief briefly described
the problem if you know it. Um, could we
look into getting it repaired or
replaced? Please let me know if you'd
like me to contact maintenance or the
supplier to arrange a fix. So, first of
all, I really like how concise it is. I
really like that there's no not a lot of
EM dashes in this. I like the um it gave
me a variable here though, which I don't
know if I'm a huge fan of actually. I
am. I think AI writing should be a bit
more. It should be AI plus human. Most
people that just copy pasted GPD4
outputs straight to jail with those.
Jesus. Like nobody wants to read your
generic like email on like oh let's dive
into the problem matter or like here are
three bullet points describing the like
I don't want to hear none of that. This
is actually good. I'm a fan of it. I'm a
fan of it. I had to think for a second
but I actually like that it's including
variables now. Um this sounds super
natural and yeah otherwise super
concise. I like it a lot. Let's look at
claude here to compare because this was
my go-to before GB5. Let's see. Coffee
machine repair needed break room. Okay.
So it just makes things up which is
fine. like it often um like that can be
useful. I think practically dayto-day
this might be more useful. Let's see. I
wanted to bring to your attention that
the coffee machine in the break room has
stopped working. It appears to have
malfunctioned this morning and is no
longer brewing coffee or dispensing hot
water. So, it's making a bunch bunch of
assumptions here. Yeah. Since many of
our team members rely on the coffee
machine throughout the day, this is
affecting productivity and morale. Okay.
Reasoning. I like that. Several
colleagues have mentioned having to
leave the office to get coffee, which
takes time away from their work. Okay,
look. So, like at this point, I'm kind
of like I'm a big fan of the fact that
there's a variable here to actually fill
in the things that GPT doesn't know from
the concept. And here it's just making
it up. Maybe maybe let me run it one
more time and see if if it does that
every time to give it a fair shot. But I
think as is, I just prefer GP5's result
here, especially with the variable. It's
just going to make the internet a better
place honestly because people will have
to think a little more. Okay, let's see.
I wanted to bring to your attention that
the coffee machine in location. Ah, so
here it's doing the same thing. So I
suppose yeah, so here it's doing the
same thing that I was a fan of. Okay, so
I guess it just depends on your luck of
the draw. Here's the optional
description. Let's see how it rounds it
out. The human factor. Please let me
know if you need any additional
information or if there's anything I can
do to help resolve this.
Yeah. So I think this is identical. This
is very identical. So on this I would
say the first one GP5 was clearly
better. Now I feel like it's just a tie.
So let's let me try one more. Um let me
try one more chat prompt here with GPT5.
Uh the chat model.
So I want to see if it does the
bracketing thing again or how this
performs. So on the second try it also
did the bracket. So I think this is a
huge upgrade. We're just going to enjoy
reading uh Twitter and LinkedIn and
everything on the internet more because
people are going to have to actually
write stuff themselves from here on out
rather than GPD40 like writing it in
that horrible robotic style every time.
Yeah, I like this a lot. So, writing
first test I would say passed equally as
good as Claude at the very least if not
better. I think it's kind of on par. I'm
really happy about this for the entirety
of the internet. Seriously, like this is
great. Okay, so that's one thing that I
wanted to test. Secondly, let's do idea
generation. Okay, to prompt this, I
write a weekly AI newsletter for 70,000
subscribers where I cover the latest in
generative AI tools and apps and
prompts. By the way, if you care link in
the description, haha, little call to
action. Generative five, generate five
distinct, varied, unique, and
interesting articles, article ideas that
blend emerging AI trends with actionable
use cases for creators and businesses.
And then I want a specific format for
each one of them. So I want a title in
quotes, a two sentence description of
the concept and its subscriber value and
at least one AI tool or new source to
feature. Okay, we're going to run this.
So basically five article ideas and then
some uh specific set of formatting.
Let's see how that does. And then I'm
going to run the same thing in cloud and
we're going to compare.
Okay, hope you're enjoying the video so
far. If you are, maybe take a second to
leave a like. Um that really helps out
the channel. But now let's compare some
of these ideas. I'm just going to give
you kind of my judgment as a content
creator in this space that you know does
this for a living and spends a lot of
time with the tools. Let's see how good
these ideas are from my perspective. So
from inspiration to income, how AI is
redefining creativity as a service. Um
subscriber value readers will learn
practical strategies to monetize AI
content at scale while protecting their
brand and IP. Okay. Using midjourney
opens GPT.
That's decent. That's decent. What else
is What else do we have? The rise of
microAI. Why small models could
outperform the giants for your business.
Okay. GPT4 and Claude make headlines.
Micro models can be trained for niche
tasks. Eh, it's okay. Problematic setup.
Problematic setup. Like, okay. Okay. Not
bad. Not bad. Um, I'll give this one
like a three stars. This one is maybe
like 3.5 stars maybe out of five.
Something like that. prototype using AI
to build and test products in days, not
months. Oh, that's actually good.
Complete mockups. Yeah, this one is
really good. Figma's AI features.
Galileo AI for not familiar. Runway for
visual prototypes. Okay, that's good. I
was thinking this was going to go more
like builder. So, these are solid ideas.
Um, I wouldn't say best I've ever heard,
but pretty good. Deep fake ads and
synthetic spokes people. This is really
good. This is I'll give this one like a
four stars. AI as your second brain
building knowledge bases that learn with
you. This is fantastic and maybe 4.5
stars just based off the title. Check
custom GPTs and vector databases. Well,
but like you can't really combine a
custom GP with a vector DB.
Okay. So, this is just like
hallucinating it. So, although it's
supposed to do that less. Yeah. Okay.
So, not bad. Let's see here. Rise of AI
voice agents.
I'm just going to kind of like brush
over this. I've run this prompt many
times in here.
I would say generally my feeling is
telling me Claude is a bit better at
this. It's just a bit better.
Just these these I don't know. You tell
me. But these titles, they just sound a
bit more clickable, a bit more
interesting, and I think it's even more
relevant. So, but it re it's really
good. I got to give it its prompts uh
props. It's really good at adhering to
the prompt. So, when you tell it
something, it's actually going to do it.
That's not the case with all models, by
the way. body spin around the block like
often you tell it like hey I want one
two three things and it's like okay I'm
going give you number one on the first
one and then forget about the others for
the rest and like it's a mess so prompt
adherence seems to be really good here I
like it the quality of the ideas
eh I don't know I'm a huge fan of claw
for ideas I think it's really good at
that um first impression of this it's
okay it's it's good um but I think the
one that many people want to see is how
does it demo with the games and how does
a demo with the physics simulations. It
looked really impressive in their
presentation. But mind you, that
presentation was crafted by one of the
biggest AI companies in the world and
they had they have hundreds if not
thousands of testers and prompters and
and they have access to the user data
and they have some of the best examples
in the world. That's my point. So what
really matters is how it performs for
your stuff, okay? And how it performs in
practice. Nevertheless, that being said,
this damn example with the castle.
Amazing. So, this is what it looked like
in their example. I ran the identical
prompt and this is what we got. I I
think you can kind of like play it and
you can pop the balloon. So, this works.
It's just graphically the other one is a
bit better with the environment and
stuff. I think they did pick an example
that it would be exceptional at, but
nevertheless, it's clearly better than
Claude here. Where are the characters?
Are they like inside of the castle? And
I can't see them. Oh, I think it placed
them like inside, but that's not really
Well, how do I I think these are the
characters. Ah, yeah, that's the noble.
But yeah, that's not amazing apparently.
So, yeah. So, GBD5 does better on this.
So, look, across the board, conclusion
time. Okay, what does this mean for free
users? What does this mean for power
users? For free users, this is
unbelievable. Like, people are going to
go from, you know, like the stone age.
They only had GPT40 which is like over
here. Okay, GPT40. GPT40
and power users with paid plans using
this on a daily they were already using
um 03 which is you know at its base like
way better but then it could search the
internet. So in some cases it was like
way better. Okay. And now GPT5 is just
just kind of did this thing. It's a
slight upgrade to 03 and all that stuff
and it makes it simpler to use. But that
combination of ease of use, it's a
fantastic illustration. No, that
combination of ease of use and its
ability to actually um perform better as
the base model and all the tools
integrated. By the way, I have to I have
to move the camera so you can see this
full thing. Make it a gamecher for free
users. Okay, GBD40 to be fair was still
pretty good, but not as good as 03. When
you have technical difficulties and it
just went into the web and thought for a
minute and found like 20 articles and
then gave you the exact response, it
feels like magic. Of felt like magic.
Claude feels like magic. Gemini feels
like magic. GBT4 did not feel like
magic. This is better than all the
competitors and it's simpler to use. So
I think for free users, complete game
changer. Please show your relatives, get
them on this on the train of of people
using this. I mean, we have 700 million
weekly active users in Chat Chipd
and now they're transitioning to this
insane. Now, for people who follow this
channel weekly, for people who use AI
daily, for people who geek out over this
stuff, this is an incremental
improvement that is very welcome. I love
that there's no more model selector. I
love that it's it looks really solid in
coding, and only time will show how good
it really is. I'll be reporting back on
use cases tomorrow and next week and the
week after like heck this is going to be
my new daily driver for now. Let's see
how that goes. I think for development
tasks where you use something like
claude code and you really go into the
deep end of the pool and you use five
agents with multiple MCPs at the same
time to build things. I think there like
claude is still king just because that
damn app works so well. But for everyday
just codewriting this might be the best
for creating quick apps. this might be
the best for helping you with writing
and everyday tasks. This is probably the
best and everybody can use it on the
free plan. So, this is going to drive
adoption. This is going to make it
easier for every single one of your
family members to actually use it. This
is going to show people what AI can
really do in 2025 rather than showing
them a little glimpse without all the
tooling and all the stuff that makes it
powerful. I think I personally think
this is a pivotal moment for AI because
the free users are going to be like
what? This is possible. You guys were
doing this all along. Or maybe they're
not even going to say that because
they're not aware. But models before
they were insane. Most people didn't
know that. Those 700 million weekly
active users, most of them, they have no
idea what the deep end of the pool looks
like. They're about to find out. For
everybody else, fantastic upgrade. Let
me know what you think though in the
comment section below. It's pretty much
everything I have for today. It's a good
little discussion. Go ahead and try it
out. Should be available. I'll put all
the links I used um in the description
below. and I will see you very